Writing code can be monotamous, sometimes difficult task.
编写代码有时候会很单调 有时候也会是复杂的任务
So I'm really a believer in setting up an environment
所以我宁愿花费比较多的时间
that you want to spend a lot of time in
来搭建一个开发环境
and that you're comfortable in when you're coding.
好让我编写代码时候更方便
That's where text editors come in.
这就是为什么需要编辑器
Because remember, the amazing thing about code is that it's just plain text.
记住 代码神奇的地方就是它只是简单的文本
So it could be written in any text file you want it.
所以你可以使用任何文本文件来编写
But people have put together some of
但是通常会有一些定制的更全面的
the most comprehensive and customizable environments to be able to write code in.
开发环境来让我们编写代码
So I quickly want to take you through my favorite and
我想向你介绍一款我最喜欢的
an industry standard which is VS Code.
符合行业标准的编辑器 VS Code
Vs Code is an app that's going to allow us to do three things right now.
VS Code 是一款软件 我们可以先使用它完成三件事
First we're going to look at how you open an existing project,
第一是打开一个现成的项目
so you can have all your files right in the code editor.
这样你可以在编辑器里面看见你所有的文件
Then we're going to show you how to create
接着我们会看看如何根据需要
a new HTML file as something you'll need to do.
创建一个新的 HTML 文件
Then I'll quickly show you through the plugin environment.
然后我会快速向你展示它的插件环境
We won't spend too much time there because,
我们不会在那里花费太多时间
literally I've spent too much time there but you
虽然我确实花费过很多时间
can really customize your setup to be anything you want.
但是你可以根据你的需要进行自定义设置
So the first thing I'm going to do,
所以第一件我们要做的事情就是
is I'm going to open Visual Code Studio,
打开 Visual Code Studio
new release notes which I'm sure are in enthralling but we'll skip for now.
这里的新发布内容可能会很有趣 但这里我们先跳过它
So one of my favorite things about getting set up here is,
我最喜欢的一个特性就是
I can just drag the folder I'm interested in working on,
我可以方便地把喜欢的文件夹拖进去
which in this case is less than one HTML,
不仅仅是一个 HTML 文件
which is where we are, and I can drop it right onto the Text Editor and it'll
这是我们的文件 然后我们把它拖拽到编辑器上
open up for me on the side all of the files
它会在旁边显示出所有的文件
that are there which makes it very easy to work with them.
这样可以让我们很方便地操作它们
Now let's say from in here I want to create a new file.
现在我们来试着创建一个新文件
One of the ways I can do it is by using the Command N shortcut.
第一种方式是可以使用 Command + N ( ctrl + N ) 快捷键
Another way is to go up here and to say 'New File'.
另一种方式是点击这里然后选择 'New File'
A third way is, I can do it here on the sidebar.
第三种方式是侧边栏这里
If I want to make a New File in my existing folder I can add a file right here.
如果我想要在这个文件夹下创建新文件 我可以点击这里
So let's add a new file.
然后添加一个新的文件
We want to learn how to make an HTML file.
我们想要学习如何创建一个 HTML file
So let's call it 'learn' and then.html.
所以我们给它命名为 learn.html
Just by adding the extension.html and saving that document it
只需要添加 .html 后缀 然后保存
knows that it is now an HTML document and can be read as such.
它就会知道这是一个 HTML 文件并读取它
So we've looked at opening a project,
现在我们已经学习了如何打开一个项目
creating an HTML file.
如何创建一个 HTML 文件
Now let's take a quick look at what some plugins do.
现在我们可以看看插件有什么功能
These are the extensions that are available in VS Code
这是你可以在 VS Code 中使用的插件
there things from themes that make your syntax highlights look different,
有些可以高亮你的语法
to Linters that will actually help you debug your code.
有些可以帮助规范你的代码使它更容易调试
Let's look for anything that has to do with HTML.
让我们看看和 HTML 相关的插件
We can see there's an HTML snippets one.
我们可以看到这有一个叫做 HTML snippets 的插件
This would allow you to create auto tags.
它可以帮助你自动创建标签
This might be something worth coming back to.
你可能会经常使用到它
Let me tell you this,
当然
installing them is easy.
安装它们也很简单
You can just press 'Install',
你只需要点击 'Install' 按钮
then I'll reset it to make sure it's activated.
然后重启编辑器使它生效就行了
Now you'd be ready to start learning how to write your HTML code,
现在你可以开始学习如何编写 HTML 代码了
right here in this file. Let's get to it
就从这个文件 让我们开始吧